- eth.dev0428@gmail.com
- ☆ 3560 Av. McCartney, Quebec, Canada
- https://personalcodecaregithub-io.vercel.app/

# Languages

**English** 

### **Interests**

Skateboarding

Coding

Cryptocurrency

#### Social networks

@personalcodecare

a

@live:.cid.f7539a6072b76e28

#### **Rob Park**

# Full Stack Developer

# Summary

I have been working as a full stack developer for 8 years, especially focus on frontend development.

Since 5 years ago, I started looking into Blockchain and Cryptocurrencies and have worked on multiple Defi projects and NFT marketplace development using Solidity, Web3.js, React, etc.

STRONG POINT:

★★★★★ Blockchain: (Smart Contract/Solidity/Ethereum)

★★★★★ Frontend: React/Redux/Thunk/NextJS + Material UI, Angular, Vue

★★★★★ Backend: NodeJS, Express, Python, Django, PHP, Laravel

★★★★ Database: MySQL, Postgres, MongoDB

# Work experience

# FullStack Blockchain Developer(Remote)

From March 2022 to September 2024 August Digital Inc. Toronto, ON, Canada

- Built NFT Marketplace of digital art on Fantom Chain. Used ERC-721, ERC-404 both for NFT, ERC-20 for governance token.
- Built token bridge between Binance and Ethereum so that users are able to migrate their NFTs from ETH to our platform.
- Implement basic functionalities of NFT Marketplace such as sale, auction, airdrop and used proxy for service fee calculation.
- Implemented NFT fractionalization so that users are able to co-won NFT and decide further steps like sale, auction, airdrop together.

## FullStack Developer (Remote)

From September 2021 to March 2022 Redux Protocol Toronto, ON, Canada

- Generate random NFT art and build the minting site using Next.js.
- Supported ongoing NFT marketplace project.
- Integrating Upgrade Farming Contract on living production.

### FullStack Blockchain Developer(Remote)

From April 2020 to August 2021 The Bridge Ltd United Kingdom

- Designed and developed the smart contracts using solidity and implemented test scripts on the smart contracts using the hardhat framework.
- Created a multithreaded Solidity application for retrieving data from blockchains and processing it for financial, statistical analysis.
- Supported ongoing projects for launch.
- Implemented Metamask, Torus, other wallets to increase user experiences.

### FullStack Web Developer(Remote)

From November 2018 to March 2020 FIXER INC Japan

- Interfaced with several crypto-exchange APIs like KuCoin, Binance, Bittrex, Huobi, and CCXT.
- Developed async implementations for asynchronous operations.
- Saved time-sensitive data into a Redis database and provided database clients to retrieve data through a simple interface.

#### **Education**

# **Bachelor of Computer Science**

From March 2012 to March 2016 Singapore University of Technology and Design Singapore